export const hard = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who directed the film 'The Lighthouse' (2019)?",
    answers: ["Ari Aster", "Jordan Peele", "Robert Eggers", "Luca Guadagnino"],
    correct_answer: "Robert Eggers",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In which film did the character 'Red' first appear?",
    answers: [
      "The Mist",
      "The Green Mile",
      "Stand By Me",
      "The Shawshank Redemption",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Shawshank Redemption",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which film features a character named 'Dr. Strangelove'?",
    answers: [
      "Paths of Glory",
      "The Day the Earth Stood Still",
      "Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb",
      "The Great Dictator",
    ],
    correct_answer:
      "Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Who won the Academy Award for Best Director for the film 'Birdman'?",
    answers: [
      "David Fincher",
      "Richard Linklater",
      "Alejandro G. Iñárritu",
      "Wes Anderson",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Alejandro G. Iñárritu",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which film is known for the quote 'I see dead people'?",
    answers: ["The Sixth Sense", "The Exorcist", "The Ring", "The Others"],
    correct_answer: "The Sixth Sense",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "In 'Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind', who plays Joel Barish?",
    answers: ["Paul Rudd", "Jim Carrey", "Jude Law", "Ethan Hawke"],
    correct_answer: "Jim Carrey",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which movie features a character named 'Klaatu'?",
    answers: [
      "War of the Worlds",
      "The Day the Earth Stood Still",
      "Close Encounters of the Third Kind",
      "The Thing",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Day the Earth Stood Still",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "In which film did Jean-Luc Godard make his directorial debut?",
    answers: ["Breathless", "Alphaville", "Contempt", "Weekend"],
    correct_answer: "Breathless",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which film features a character named 'Gollum'?",
    answers: [
      "Pan's Labyrinth",
      "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows",
      "The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey",
      "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Who played the role of the 'Man with No Name' in Sergio Leone's trilogy?",
    answers: [
      "Kurt Russell",
      "Lee Van Cleef",
      "Clint Eastwood",
      "Charles Bronson",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Clint Eastwood",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "In 'Mulholland Drive', who is revealed to be the real identity of Betty Elms?",
    answers: ["Diane Selwyn", "Camilla Rhodes", "Alice", "Rita"],
    correct_answer: "Diane Selwyn",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "In 'The Master', who plays the role of Freddie Quell?",
    answers: [
      "Paul Thomas Anderson",
      "Adam Sandler",
      "Philip Seymour Hoffman",
      "Joaquin Phoenix",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Joaquin Phoenix",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Which film depicts the true story of the 'Blackfish' controversy?",
    answers: [
      "The Ivory Game",
      "March of the Penguins",
      "The Cove",
      "Blackfish",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Blackfish",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Who directed the film 'The Third Man' (1949)?",
    answers: ["Carol Reed", "John Huston", "Orson Welles", "Alfred Hitchcock"],
    correct_answer: "Carol Reed",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "In 'The Grand Budapest Hotel', who is the author of the book that the film is based on?",
    answers: ["Stefan Zweig", "Ray Bradbury", "Agnes Varda", "Wes Anderson"],
    correct_answer: "Stefan Zweig",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "Which film features a character named 'The Bride' seeking revenge?",
    answers: [
      "Pulp Fiction",
      "The Killers",
      "Kill Bill: Vol. 1",
      "The Professional",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Kill Bill: Vol. 1",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      "In 'The Seventh Seal', what game does the knight play with Death?",
    answers: ["Cards", "Checkers", "Chess", "Backgammon"],
    correct_answer: "Chess",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Which film is known for the quote 'Here's looking at you, kid'?",
    answers: [
      "Casablanca",
      "Gone with the Wind",
      "The Maltese Falcon",
      "To Have and Have Not",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Casablanca",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "Who directed the film 'Solaris' (1972)?",
    answers: [
      "Ingmar Bergman",
      "Stanley Kubrick",
      "Akira Kurosawa",
      "Andrei Tarkovsky",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Andrei Tarkovsky",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question:
      "In 'A Clockwork Orange', what is the name of the main character?",
    answers: ["Ludovico", "Alex DeLarge", "Droogs", "Malcolm McDowell"],
    correct_answer: "Alex DeLarge",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "In 'The Elephant Man', who plays the role of John Merrick?",
    answers: ["David Lynch", "Jack Nance", "Anthony Hopkins", "John Hurt"],
    correct_answer: "John Hurt",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "Which film features a character named 'Rhett Butler'?",
    answers: [
      "Casablanca",
      "Gone with the Wind",
      "The Wizard of Oz",
      "Rebecca",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Gone with the Wind",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question:
      "Who directed the film 'La Jetée' (1962), a film made almost entirely of still photographs?",
    answers: [
      "Jean-Luc Godard",
      "Alain Resnais",
      "Chris Marker",
      "Agnes Varda",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Chris Marker",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "Which film features a character named 'Howard Beale'?",
    answers: ["The Fountainhead", "Citizen Kane", "Network", "The Big Sleep"],
    correct_answer: "Network",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question:
      "In 'Inception', what is the name of the device used to enter dreams?",
    answers: [
      "The Dream Machine",
      "The Hypnograph",
      "The PASIV Device",
      "The Somnaculator",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The PASIV Device",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question:
      "In which film does the protagonist navigate a post-apocalyptic world while dealing with an illness that has left humanity on the brink of extinction?",
    answers: ["Children of Men", "The Road", "I Am Legend", "A Quiet Place"],
    correct_answer: "Children of Men",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "Which film features a character named 'The Kid'?",
    answers: ["Modern Times", "The Great Dictator", "City Lights", "The Kid"],
    correct_answer: "The Kid",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "In 'Blue Velvet', who plays the character of Jeffrey Beaumont?",
    answers: [
      "Laura Dern",
      "Kyle MacLachlan",
      "Isabella Rossellini",
      "Dennis Hopper",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Kyle MacLachlan",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question:
      "Which film features the quote 'We all go a little mad sometimes'?",
    answers: ["The Birds", "Rosemary's Baby", "The Shining", "Psycho"],
    correct_answer: "Psycho",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "Who directed the film 'Bitter Moon' (1992)?",
    answers: [
      "François Truffaut",
      "Roman Polanski",
      "Michelangelo Antonioni",
      "Pedro Almodóvar",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Roman Polanski",
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question:
      "Which film depicts the life of the French sculptor Camille Claudel?",
    answers: [
      "The Artist",
      "Camille Claudel",
      "La Belle Époque",
      "L'Amour Fou",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Camille Claudel",
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: "In 'Persona', who plays the role of Elisabet Vogler?",
    answers: [
      "Bibi Andersson",
      "Liv Ullmann",
      "Ingrid Thulin",
      "Harriet Andersson",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Liv Ullmann",
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "Who directed 'The Last Emperor' (1987)?",
    answers: [
      "Bernardo Bertolucci",
      "Martin Scorsese",
      "David Lynch",
      "Ingmar Bergman",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Bernardo Bertolucci",
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question:
      "In 'The Double Life of Veronique', which character is portrayed by Irene Jacob?",
    answers: ["Weronika", "Veronique", "Anne", "Monique"],
    correct_answer: "Veronique",
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question:
      "Which film features a fictional account of the making of a Shakespearean play?",
    answers: [
      "Shakespeare in Love",
      "The Other Boleyn Girl",
      "Elizabeth",
      "Anonymous",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Shakespeare in Love",
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "Who composed the score for the film '2001: A Space Odyssey'?",
    answers: [
      "John Williams",
      "Stanley Kubrick",
      "Gustav Holst",
      "Richard Strauss",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Gustav Holst",
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "Which film features a dystopian future where books are burned?",
    answers: ["Fahrenheit 451", "Brave New World", "Gattaca", "Equilibrium"],
    correct_answer: "Fahrenheit 451",
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: "In 'The Big Lebowski', what is the name of the bowling team?",
    answers: ["The Nihilists", "The Dude Abides", "The Strikes", "The Jesus"],
    correct_answer: "The Dude Abides",
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "Who directed the film 'The Passion of Joan of Arc' (1928)?",
    answers: [
      "Carl Theodor Dreyer",
      "Fritz Lang",
      "Georg Wilhelm Pabst",
      "Ernst Lubitsch",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Carl Theodor Dreyer",
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question: "Which film is set in the city of Bruges?",
    answers: ["In Bruges", "The Tourist", "Bruges", "The European"],
    correct_answer: "In Bruges",
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    question: "Who directed 'The Red Shoes' (1948)?",
    answers: [
      "Michael Powell and Emeric Pressburger",
      "Alfred Hitchcock",
      "David Lean",
      "Cecil B. DeMille",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Michael Powell and Emeric Pressburger",
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: "In 'The Holy Mountain', who is the director?",
    answers: [
      "Federico Fellini",
      "Alejandro Jodorowsky",
      "Luis Buñuel",
      "Jean-Luc Godard",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Alejandro Jodorowsky",
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: "Which film features the character 'The Man Who Fell to Earth'?",
    answers: [
      "The Man Who Fell to Earth",
      "Dark Star",
      "Blade Runner",
      "Starman",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Man Who Fell to Earth",
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question: "In 'The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari', who is the main antagonist?",
    answers: ["Cesare", "Dr. Caligari", "Jane", "Alan"],
    correct_answer: "Dr. Caligari",
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question:
      "Which film features a dystopian future with a society of extreme surveillance?",
    answers: ["Blade Runner", "The Fifth Element", "Brazil", "Minority Report"],
    correct_answer: "Brazil",
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question: "Who directed 'The Umbrellas of Cherbourg' (1964)?",
    answers: [
      "Jacques Demy",
      "François Truffaut",
      "Jean-Luc Godard",
      "Agnès Varda",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Jacques Demy",
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question: "In 'Raging Bull', who plays the role of Jake LaMotta?",
    answers: ["Robert De Niro", "Al Pacino", "Joe Pesci", "Martin Scorsese"],
    correct_answer: "Robert De Niro",
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question: "Which film features a character named 'Frank Abagnale Jr.'?",
    answers: [
      "Catch Me If You Can",
      "The Great Gatsby",
      "The Sting",
      "American Hustle",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Catch Me If You Can",
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "Who directed 'The Holy Mountain' (1973)?",
    answers: [
      "Luis Buñuel",
      "Alejandro Jodorowsky",
      "Federico Fellini",
      "Jean-Luc Godard",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Alejandro Jodorowsky",
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question:
      "Which film is set in a post-apocalyptic wasteland and features a 'Mad Max' character?",
    answers: [
      "Mad Max: Fury Road",
      "The Road Warrior",
      "Waterworld",
      "Children of Men",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Mad Max: Fury Road",
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    question:
      "Which film features a character who is a former child prodigy struggling with a mathematical theorem?",
    answers: [
      "Good Will Hunting",
      "A Beautiful Mind",
      "The Imitation Game",
      "The Theory of Everything",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Good Will Hunting",
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    question: "Which film is known for its groundbreaking use of color?",
    answers: [
      "The Wizard of Oz",
      "Gone with the Wind",
      "The Adventures of Robin Hood",
      "Fantasia",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Wizard of Oz",
  },
  {
    id: 53,
    question:
      "What is the name of the film that is a quasi-remake of Fritz Lang's 'Metropolis' and features a dystopian future where the ruling class lives in luxury above a grimy working class?",
    answers: ["Blade Runner", "Gattaca", "Brazil", "The Fifth Element"],
    correct_answer: "Blade Runner",
  },
  {
    id: 54,
    question:
      "Which film is known for its innovative use of a non-linear narrative structure, intertwining multiple storylines across different characters and time periods?",
    answers: ["Pulp Fiction", "Memento", "The Prestige", "Cloud Atlas"],
    correct_answer: "Cloud Atlas",
  },
  {
    id: 55,
    question: "Who directed the film 'Wings of Desire' (1987)?",
    answers: [
      "Werner Herzog",
      "Rainer Werner Fassbinder",
      "Michael Haneke",
      "Wim Wenders",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Wim Wenders",
  },
  {
    id: 56,
    question:
      "In 'The Double Life of Veronique', which character is portrayed by Irene Jacob?",
    answers: ["Anne", "Veronique", "Monique", "Weronika"],
    correct_answer: "Veronique",
  },
  {
    id: 57,
    question:
      "Which director is known for his distinctive use of long takes, including a famous 17-minute sequence shot in a film about a war hero?",
    answers: [
      "Alfred Hitchcock",
      "Stanley Kubrick",
      "Andrei Tarkovsky",
      "Paul Thomas Anderson",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Andrei Tarkovsky",
  },
  {
    id: 58,
    question: "Who directed the film 'The Third Man' (1949)?",
    answers: ["John Huston", "Carol Reed", "Orson Welles", "Alfred Hitchcock"],
    correct_answer: "Carol Reed",
  },
  {
    id: 59,
    question:
      "What is the name of the film that features a character who is a struggling writer who has to cope with his own dark past while trying to succeed in the literary world?",
    answers: ["The Shining", "The Hours", "A Beautiful Mind", "The Bell Jar"],
    correct_answer: "The Hours",
  },
  {
    id: 60,
    question:
      "In which film does the protagonist attempt to solve a series of complex puzzles left by a deceased inventor?",
    answers: [
      "The Da Vinci Code",
      "The Maze Runner",
      "Ready Player One",
      "Inception",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Ready Player One",
  },
  {
    id: 61,
    question:
      "Which film tells the story of a man who experiences a series of events that challenge his perception of reality and control?",
    answers: ["The Matrix", "Fight Club", "Donnie Darko", "The Truman Show"],
    correct_answer: "The Truman Show",
  },
  {
    id: 62,
    question: "What is the central theme of the film 'Synecdoche, New York'?",
    answers: [
      "Identity and existence",
      "Love and loss",
      "Time and memory",
      "Success and failure",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Identity and existence",
  },
  {
    id: 63,
    question:
      "Which film features a protagonist who is a brilliant surgeon with a hidden past who must navigate a complex moral dilemma?",
    answers: [
      "The Prestige",
      "The Invisible Man",
      "The Constant Gardener",
      "The Skin I Live In",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Skin I Live In",
  },
  {
    id: 64,
    question:
      "Which director is known for his unique approach to storytelling, often incorporating elements of fantasy and reality in his films?",
    answers: [
      "Guillermo del Toro",
      "Tim Burton",
      "David Lynch",
      "Wes Anderson",
    ],
    correct_answer: "David Lynch",
  },
  {
    id: 65,
    question:
      "In which film does a character discover a hidden society that exists within our own, influencing major events from behind the scenes?",
    answers: [
      "The Adjustment Bureau",
      "Dark City",
      "The Matrix",
      "The Illusionist",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Dark City",
  },
  {
    id: 66,
    question:
      "Which film explores the life of a reclusive artist who hides behind a mask and has a secret that could change the art world forever?",
    answers: [
      "The Phantom of the Opera",
      "The Great Beauty",
      "The Artist",
      "The Mask of Zorro",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Phantom of the Opera",
  },
  {
    id: 67,
    question:
      "Which film features a dystopian future with a society of extreme surveillance?",
    answers: ["Brazil", "Minority Report", "The Fifth Element", "Gattaca"],
    correct_answer: "Brazil",
  },
  {
    id: 68,
    question: "Who directed the film 'Solaris' (1972)?",
    answers: [
      "Stanley Kubrick",
      "Akira Kurosawa",
      "Andrei Tarkovsky",
      "Ingmar Bergman",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Andrei Tarkovsky",
  },
  {
    id: 69,
    question:
      "Which film features the quote 'The stuff that dreams are made of'?",
    answers: [
      "Casablanca",
      "The Maltese Falcon",
      "To Have and Have Not",
      "The Big Sleep",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Maltese Falcon",
  },
  {
    id: 70,
    question:
      "In 'The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari', what is the profession of the main character?",
    answers: ["Artist", "Psychiatrist", "Magician", "Journalist"],
    correct_answer: "Psychiatrist",
  },
  {
    id: 71,
    question:
      "Which film explores the concept of a computer's sentience and its consequences?",
    answers: ["Her", "2001: A Space Odyssey", "Ex Machina", "Blade Runner"],
    correct_answer: "2001: A Space Odyssey",
  },
  {
    id: 72,
    question: "In 'The Holy Mountain', who plays the role of the Alchemist?",
    answers: [
      "Luis Buñuel",
      "David Lynch",
      "Alejandro Jodorowsky",
      "Federico Fellini",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Alejandro Jodorowsky",
  },
  {
    id: 73,
    question:
      "Which film is known for its unique use of color and set design, directed by Jean-Pierre Jeunet?",
    answers: ["City of Lost Children", "Delicatessen", "Micmacs", "Amélie"],
    correct_answer: "Amélie",
  },
  {
    id: 74,
    question: "Who directed the 1967 film 'The Graduate'?",
    answers: [
      "Francis Ford Coppola",
      "Mike Nichols",
      "Stanley Kubrick",
      "Richard Lester",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Mike Nichols",
  },
  {
    id: 75,
    question: "Which film features a character named 'Sam Spade'?",
    answers: [
      "Murder My Sweet",
      "The Thin Man",
      "The Big Sleep",
      "The Maltese Falcon",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Maltese Falcon",
  },
  {
    id: 76,
    question: "In 'The Seventh Seal', what does the knight challenge Death to?",
    answers: ["A game of chess", "A game of cards", "A footrace", "A duel"],
    correct_answer: "A game of chess",
  },
  {
    id: 77,
    question:
      "Which film is set in a dystopian future with a totalitarian regime and features 'Winston Smith'?",
    answers: ["Fahrenheit 451", "1984", "Equilibrium", "Brave New World"],
    correct_answer: "1984",
  },
  {
    id: 78,
    question: "Who played the role of the 'Joker' in 'The Dark Knight' (2008)?",
    answers: [
      "Heath Ledger",
      "Christian Bale",
      "Mark Ruffalo",
      "Aaron Eckhart",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Heath Ledger",
  },
  {
    id: 79,
    question: "In 'The Big Lebowski', who is known as 'The Dude'?",
    answers: ["Walter Sobchak", "Jeff Lebowski", "The Dude", "Donny"],
    correct_answer: "Jeff Lebowski",
  },
  {
    id: 80,
    question:
      "Which film directed by Jean-Luc Godard features the character 'Michel Poiccard'?",
    answers: ["Breathless", "Contempt", "Pierrot le Fou", "Alphaville"],
    correct_answer: "Breathless",
  },
  {
    id: 81,
    question: "In 'Wings of Desire', what is the main character's occupation?",
    answers: ["Angel", "Poet", "Photographer", "Actor"],
    correct_answer: "Angel",
  },
  {
    id: 82,
    question:
      "Which film directed by Yasujiro Ozu features the character 'Noriko'?",
    answers: [
      "An Autumn Afternoon",
      "Tokyo Story",
      "The End of Summer",
      "Late Spring",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Late Spring",
  },
  {
    id: 83,
    question: "Who directed the film 'The Exterminating Angel' (1962)?",
    answers: [
      "Federico Fellini",
      "Jean-Luc Godard",
      "Luis Buñuel",
      "Alain Resnais",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Luis Buñuel",
  },
  {
    id: 84,
    question:
      "In 'The Royal Tenenbaums', who plays the role of Margot Tenenbaum?",
    answers: [
      "Gwyneth Paltrow",
      "Frances McDormand",
      "Angelica Huston",
      "Catherine Zeta-Jones",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Gwyneth Paltrow",
  },
  {
    id: 85,
    question:
      "Which film features a character named 'Nino' who is a professional pickpocket?",
    answers: [
      "The 400 Blows",
      "The Bicycle Thieves",
      "Rififi",
      "The Third Man",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Rififi",
  },
  {
    id: 86,
    question: "Who directed the film 'The Piano' (1993)?",
    answers: [
      "Agnes Varda",
      "Jane Campion",
      "Sofia Coppola",
      "Lina Wertmüller",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Jane Campion",
  },
  {
    id: 87,
    question:
      "Which film is known for the line 'I'm going to make him an offer he can't refuse'?",
    answers: ["Goodfellas", "Scarface", "Casino", "The Godfather"],
    correct_answer: "The Godfather",
  },
  {
    id: 88,
    question: "In 'Raging Bull', who plays the role of Jake LaMotta?",
    answers: [
      "Joe Pesci",
      "Paul Schrader",
      "Martin Scorsese",
      "Robert De Niro",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Robert De Niro",
  },
  {
    id: 89,
    question:
      "Which film, directed by Stanley Kubrick, is set in a dystopian future with violent gangs?",
    answers: [
      "2001: A Space Odyssey",
      "Full Metal Jacket",
      "The Shining",
      "A Clockwork Orange",
    ],
    correct_answer: "A Clockwork Orange",
  },
  {
    id: 90,
    question:
      "Who directed 'La Dolce Vita' (1960), a film known for its depiction of the Roman upper class?",
    answers: [
      "Michelangelo Antonioni",
      "Federico Fellini",
      "Giuseppe Tornatore",
      "Luchino Visconti",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Federico Fellini",
  },
  {
    id: 91,
    question: "Which film features a character named 'Gollum'?",
    answers: [
      "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
      "Pan's Labyrinth",
      "The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey",
      "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers",
  },
  {
    id: 92,
    question: "In 'The Third Man', who plays the role of Harry Lime?",
    answers: ["Alida Valli", "Joseph Cotten", "Bernard Lee", "Orson Welles"],
    correct_answer: "Orson Welles",
  },
  {
    id: 93,
    question: "Which film features a dystopian future where books are burned?",
    answers: ["Minority Report", "Gattaca", "Total Recall", "Fahrenheit 451"],
    correct_answer: "Fahrenheit 451",
  },
  {
    id: 94,
    question:
      "Who directed 'The Fountainhead' (1949) based on the novel by Ayn Rand?",
    answers: ["King Vidor", "Alfred Hitchcock", "John Ford", "Orson Welles"],
    correct_answer: "King Vidor",
  },
  {
    id: 95,
    question: "In 'M', who is the main antagonist?",
    answers: [
      "A police detective",
      "A serial killer",
      "A politician",
      "A judge",
    ],
    correct_answer: "A serial killer",
  },
  {
    id: 96,
    question:
      "Which film by Jean-Pierre Jeunet features a character named 'Amélie'?",
    answers: ["Delicatessen", "City of Lost Children", "Micmacs", "Amélie"],
    correct_answer: "Amélie",
  },
  {
    id: 97,
    question: "In 'Spirited Away', what is the main character's name?",
    answers: ["Chihiro", "Satsuki", "Kiki", "Haku"],
    correct_answer: "Chihiro",
  },
  {
    id: 98,
    question: "Who directed the film 'Rashomon' (1950)?",
    answers: [
      "Yasujiro Ozu",
      "Akira Kurosawa",
      "Kenji Mizoguchi",
      "Hiroshi Shimizu",
    ],
    correct_answer: "Akira Kurosawa",
  },
  {
    id: 99,
    question:
      "Which film by Ingmar Bergman features the character 'The Knight'?",
    answers: [
      "The Virgin Spring",
      "Cries and Whispers",
      "The Seventh Seal",
      "Wild Strawberries",
    ],
    correct_answer: "The Seventh Seal",
  },
  {
    id: 100,
    question:
      "In 'Blade Runner', what is the term used for the bioengineered beings?",
    answers: ["Replicants", "Cyborgs", "Humanoids", "Androids"],
    correct_answer: "Replicants",
  },
];
